buyitsellit.com 2003-04-01

# BuyItSellIt.com Auctions and Classifieds: Don't Pay Unless You Sell!

**BuyItSellIt.com Corporate Information:  
Privacy Statement and Information for our Users** |  |  BuyItSellIt.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: BuyItSellIt.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your user session and to gather broad demographic information.   
  
---|---  
  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. 

When necessary, customer information can also be shared with parties to assist in contact related to transactions arranged within BuyItSellIt.com's marketplace. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys ask visitors for financial information (like their account or credit card numbers) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Children's Guidelines

According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program.

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@buyitsellit.com](mailto:webmaster@buyitsellit.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [webmaster@buyitsellit.com](mailto:webmaster@buyitsellit.com)' 
  2. Log into "My Home" and edit contact preference to be removed from any contact from us. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Kyle Wilgus BuyItSellIt.com 117 Hall Street Suite C Santa Cruz, CA 95062 kwilgus@buyitsellit.com  
  
**Featured BuyItSellIt.com StoreFronts**  
---  
Visit our Featured [BuyItSellIt.com StoreFronts](http://store.buyitsellit.com/) and take advantage of their special offers.  

| **GardenBuilt.com:**   **Quality birding products and garden accessories**  
Bird feeders, nestboxes and garden planters built to beautify and last.  

| **Bulldog Plumbing.com :**  **Plumbing fixtures and supplies for less**  
Brand name faucets, sinks and bathroom accessories with free shipping.  

| **RP Golf :**  **Handmade golf clubs for all golfers**  
Let Master Clubmaker Rick Prose build the clubs of your dreams
